I welcome back to the wheel of life
online between a llama that become a
leader a parent online Radek a to pun
and now we've reached session 11
skyrocket
Masuka surcease oblasts and this session
is called how it all begins sustained it
is somewhat buggy - ammonia de Molay the
outline that we talked about at the
beginning of this retreat
Kisaragi table each other cut the oil
referent in me we reviewed some of the
past retreats we've been doing lately
katomina proper etiquette a la coka we
covered you know how do negative
emotions come up in your mind get humbly
put bogeyman I am mostly negative moon
chill girl a beacon on kita then we
covered how did those cause I still
collect karma company in Cataumet
Shakopee bagaimana - minion Bob cranky
toboggan book on karma then we saw how
those Karma's take us through a whole
life even to death and to the Bardo into
the next birth
now looky Tommy hot bagaimana karma
carmine to Milwaukee Tom lala-lulu he
due back on some pie mati that kobato
that Calliope
Brigid there and then sub-aqua
appreciate the teacher of this of this
whole book company and Ibaka Rinpoche
guru there is little boo Queenie he said
let's go look at another way this is to
presented for example by the first
pension really obokata Mariquita melihat
Sara
Lyon howleen is this a chicken masala
panchen lama retama
and just a cup
je tsongkhapa and they like to use the
wheel of life to come back a new button
so we're gonna start out with the wheel
of life teaching we're gonna go through
the wheel of life teaching now kita akan
molybdenum higher and Rhoda kinda but
that is cultures as the image is it's a
blind woman it's an elderly woman who is
who cannot see well dance I am Amelia
baggy gambar soren Juanita buta sort of
own it up to yr kidnapped Amelia taken
by him for me personally this represents
my stepmom buggy science are everybody
anymore Killebrew teary Sonya ever since
lost my real mother
toxic element EBU condo SIA my stepmom
Edie
booty fire Edie she married my father
Dominick cardigan is aya and she's had a
long beautiful life she's a very fine
person that can open up and jungin in
DES
and then now she's losing her eyesight
yeah sekarang map animal abuta and they
did many operations
lakukan by nichole proxy and they said
no the cannot fix it kappa gaby sada
prabh a key and she's she's slowly
becoming climb Ranma JD buta and I
stopped her two days ago several
barbiturate Agana do her in LA and she
keeps falling down she keeps tripping on
things
dos mundos chatted entre Sandow
she has trouble seeing steps for example
Mahalo maker Selita Lanka cockiness
never have another close friend I'm
going to show you his picture now he's
got a steel side you can put your thumb
in the cut line yeah
Sacramento chicken for Tonya not mine
yucky oh he's kind of our son Veronica I
mean that's that's our sauce but they're
not coming for any content sigh aspirin
economy and he's an old dog yeah say
could I do that
somebody kind of dumped him on us just
on some protein eunbong a coke on me and
we're afraid that those people would
kill him then committee talkin mudanya
so we agreed to take him did he come his
pocket automobile and the problem is I
don't know if you can see where he's
blind
that muscle honest I got a pocket of
easily hot tre to butta
he's also dead to come Dooley so his
life is very difficult he duped us
actually you see another picture of him
here in Cumberland our idea duccini
outside our house Giroux Mikami and he's
headed towards a big piece of wood
behind the I'm gonna do cause pop catch
him because he will hit his head this
drawing people blind animal tiny heroin
buta they have trouble break up with a
masala because they cannot see condom
riccati that we suddenly had they get
into danger when I come oscar de la
bahia dangerous situations happens it
was super bahia tragedy pad america and
that's the story of the first link of
the wheel of Laden in Tula treated air
it out and / tomorrow depend upon and
here we see the first picture of the
wheel basilica Tom had number pertama
Daria Rhonda and it's a painting of a
blind man with a stick - Lucas answer
and Priya booted in an tonka and this in
the Wheel of Life represents the first
link in the we are the first of the
twelve links the Lambada k du pineal
about Kenyatta mother into a blessed
out'n which is called misunderstood nice
Abud Casa La Palma and people have
called it ignorant for our army a
butcher cut the doctor one which is sort
of a translation of the Sanskrit which
is a video young group a consumer
chapter to man vs. also curtain is about
a media which literally means not seeing
means no art in a terribly hot RRP the
dealer is related video with Miss Kitty
see video Berkut another video Umbra
tamale huh
and it and it means people have
translated as ignorance than diamond of
Jamaica and somebody cut it uptown one
so I want you there wherever you're
sitting right now
saya ingin Under the Sun a teaming up on
Anderson to Duke's Karen watching this
video not on video evening I'd like you
to think for a minute about the
difference
sighing another precursor General Patton
promenade what's the difference between
the word ignorance in the world
misunderstood a proper bed and ricotta
patty doctor Wadud cutter cuts Alabama
and in the abhidharma which then is
again is translating that the a
biedermeyer studies language amok on his
schedule to finish in 26 years
the aditya wattle catwalk her suicidal
abroad balloon um Tahoe
it says ignorance if you think about it
is for example like you don't know a
certain person decapitated that tall one
you gotta pick your tom hollie total
Super T under the duck town so sore
important to so I was thinking about a
friend in my college time named her son
Tony a cyber pecan phantom and some of
to cooling Bernama Tom you know as
telling the in denote cyber Pena Stanley
and I cannot Tom he say no guess I
wasn't even born as they belong $80 a
box a blah blah up audacity to so that's
not knowing term you to get up manga now
tom
a video or ignorance avidya Authority
doctor one you know I just don't know
him that's so that's one kind of not
knowing it was optimistic uptown but if
I said it Stanley do you know the term
color sign butter katakana Stanley and
about Tom and I'm thinking about the
term that I knew when I was in college
and somebody kept among Thomas I can
also walk to Masuku Lea and in Stanley
misunderstands my questioning and he
thinks I'm talking about some time that
we both know now this then commenced and
assalam o Muhammad Perpignan SIA and
Deepika fire bro Tonya barbiturate
UNASUR Antonio Gita Purdue I could now
sardini then he says yeah I know
la lluvia broke after I set out tapa he
doesn't understand I'm talking about the
term from a hundred years ago a period
of December which are attendant on him
there is reduced on ela leu so now it's
different
Scarborough villain in the first case
Salim Casas pertama I said do you know
the term that was in my college saya
punya upon that autumn what - fire
deeper grunting he he says no I wasn't
born here again they belong blooms
abloom liar geshe-la if I just say do
you know turn at all sigh hanumakonda
Tommy mom he make Stanley makes a
mistake not lost anymore but Kassala ha
and he thinks I'm talking about another
term done because I said Anubis are
attending lawyer so miss understanding
it to xalapa and that's different from
not knowing the little blue bitter
doesn't it at my house Tom in the first
click case ignorance or not knowing
Crusoe's pertama cut the doctor one
attitude of Tao it's just that you don't
know this person under sadhya under D
terminal or a Guinea
but with miss knowing misunderstand the
doctor wants all up on our pian it's
more dangerous and it'll be a bit of a
higher so for example he might go to
that tum the new time and say okay so I
says you went to college together
did he be selenium punkin me Jerry Tom
borrow that Brocato geshe-la monitor
commander copper grunting Ibrahim will
get us sir I wasn't even born at that
time
Oh Tommy took at Marist I'm backin blah
blah here but I walked Ito so it's easy
to imagine this picture of a blind
person or a blind dog the d buddha by a
can cover or on boot Otto engine boot I
to their life is a kind of darkness see
the micro so much I'm Google of fun
they cannot even see Tom for example
acaba can't even be somebody from Sonya
but that's not actually what we're
talking about in the Wheel of Life
appear to become an arbiter up and get a
Eric Andy Roddick a Hadoop but
we're talking about you miss understand
so really it's not that you're blind is
that you are seeing something that's not
there
Casa La Palma and Jodi Buchan bratty and
Abu Taha Nia and Emily have so Swati and
peanut butter
in and then you get in trouble because
the whole topic we are covering in the
alarm room right now is how you get in
trouble
Thank You mood inaudible had a pea
masala Karnas Lulu topic and Italy put
in the lamrim and a la terre under the
pot masala
so we're gonna go back to the text now
did he get that kinda Kabbalah context a
car run and we're gonna read it together
thank you talking about Sonya but summer
Samba please keep that in mind
Pepito longing I did too I always
translate a video or Reaper as
misunderstanding Solomon Durga back on a
video at american bugei casa la palma
noticing because somebody cut it up now
one it doesn't mean you don't know it
will deter property entity rock town it
means you miss know it abruptly under
xalapa you think you know what you don't
know under picker and earth out of unity
duck town and that's more danger the
need to libel bahia okay here we go with
the text ok the scenic atomic attacks
tombow magic bunny means let's talk
about the first of the twelve links mari
kita bisa Ratan Tata Madrid Oblast Alton
and this is as we said misunderstanding
xalapa Hoffman in public Ramsey says
core work awaits our in makka pakka
Makka pakka
it means this is the main cause or the
root of why we are circling around the
circle of suffering life in Eliyahu
tomorrow our charter a monopoly
tubercular parte de la winger and
panduranga Dupin
now the purpose of studying the ancient
books for example if you come to the
mixed nuts classes currently buku buku
thomas illogical and the hardy class
class mix that's a Turkish example run
is to develop wisdom we call shooter
Adelanto manga mechanically oksanen and
get us about shehram
it sounds good it's called press near
the lamb Sanskrit mussels carpaccio but
Brian you know it came to be pronounced
bora-bora bono Middleborough gondola
bizarre Chinese disabled person
aparajita so this wisdom that he could
be Jackson on any it has a special
meaning in Buddhism wisdom in general in
English is like the diligence of an old
man from living a long life to be a son
and animo Milla chaotic Usos de la boule
is more than pandemonium Jocelyn Ptolemy
ingress broth because as a protocol
services or on prayer to America he do
penang Pancham
and when we say wisdom in Buddhism
epicatechin katomina toxin and alum
Buddhist MA it has a different flavor
the AMA militarism bro beta and it means
you see the real nature of the world
around you
arti neodermyl have curd and Astley
duniya discrete or under
and here it says shut up k-dog may
pursue more
what does wisdom see traditional decay
darken up I am Dilli Haat
only objection that meta means it says
that things are not themselves doc
people are TDR melihat segalis us what
to Boogedy recent theory and I loved the
example that we learned when we go to
the diamond cutter Institute programs
and sassou cut something get up player
plagiarism on akuti program diamond
cutter
which is called there's a life tool they
called a life tool called the two
husbands in the kitchen dalla preyed
upon life tool the only support to us
WOM ended up poor
and it's the story where a woman yells
and her two kids on a Friday I need to
add a lot Sarita Soren Juanita Bert
react but I'd wanna camp and hurry to
mom and she hears herself inside the
abandoned our pier in Hobart Aria which
plans has seen in her mind I'm gonna be
beadalon PK run now
next week bingo BRE good now she comes
home the appalling Roma she walks in the
kitchen Virgil and kadapa and her
husband immediately yells at her and
caused her stupid Shawn Minister Ghulam
Sagar amun-re akadama Manila Bhutto it
is easy for that woman to think oh my
husband yelled at me for no reason
Hudiburg even a tie to the particulars
from me sorry Bert react but as I
attempt Alison I didn't even say
anything and he call me stupid luma
katakana Papa daddy up among girls abode
oh so she's seeing a husband in front of
her JD d obligate Sarang Swamy did a
punya who is yelling her your stupid
Yammer tripod on yonder Buddha for no
good reason and bad Alesana papa and she
and us we will always say I didn't do
anything
Thank You Todd and keep touching up a
condom a lot gonna pop on yes I am that
mind which thinks their husbands yelling
at me for no reason
it's Koran peaking at number peak of
Swami but preferred si upon powerless
son
that state of mind is link number one
it's misunderstood couldn't be garanito
della total number sad to Salah Bahama
where is it misunderstanding Apostle
Appa doesn't understand that that
husband came from the scene in my own
mind carbonated among our people was
Swami that under ibid LMP current size
sendiri
it doesn't understand I planted that
seed in my own mind last week when I
yelled at my kids did a monarchy
mahasaya mañana medellín picker
ancillary mingle Alok Atticus I
appropriate pada anaconda
so there's actually a second husband in
the kitchen this um Daria - Swami can do
added up or which did come from her
yeah but urban are top and area came
from the city and Herman Dabra tsaldari
be patella picky Rania that one really
exists no subtitle banana rata it's like
the teacher we meditated on in the
previous session supporting guru young
cat emeritus abrahama
de midi did alum says is abloom yeah i
did these beautiful things in my past
life so i am la coka holland i medical
pond masala loser acid that I see this
beautiful teacher and car - Emily had
green dye name that's dependent
origination
it'll sub up a Cuban I yelled at my kids
cyber trap under Annapurna
and depending on dad came my husband and
karate Oh muchos a messiah
who is yelling at me yeah Bert react by
the fire and a person who understands
that that's a sort of a monarchy to who
has wisdom young impunity Oxana they
walk in the kitchen cooking America
Burchell and kadar porn the husband says
the years to transfer me back after on
de Bordeaux and immediately this emotion
comes up that's a grimace any mutual why
he comes to nobody pamungkas Papa she
she's able to stop that emotion happy
dear Mum pamoja taken MOC
because she attended the online we love
life retreat karna yamaja dear entrant
online road acadia pond she understands
that husband who is not her fault is not
real diamond our team our Swami ammu
cancel on it to tell ekkada
if you want to sail in a mysterious way
to kendama ingen Monacan an entirely
mysterious she understands the husband
she thought was there was not there she
understands her husband is nervous young
artists from me young appear under the
Sun I do somebody other Tina Canada
sauna P among artists forming a new book
insomnia and that's what the normal
means here then it'll IND buckshot
lamrim listening when it says
ghotakamukha talkin sherab key dom a
person
your wisdom perceives kabhi oksana non
non biyori subset the person is not the
person Baha'i to book an or Anya now you
know what that means sohcahtoa
a party the person who didn't come from
you in the kitchen is not a person or a
soul very under the debris to buchan
horror now there's an important word
here
la la its current under cutter putting
this in ela ela is not Los Angeles Los
Angeles okay it means for our pina puppy
wisdom understands the husband in the
kitchen who years are made for no reason
doesn't exist could be excited mama ha
me Swami did a poem but threat but as I
attack powerless on e2t dadada
but misunderstanding poppy xalapa link
number 1 in the numbers are too dear a
decade apart it is why is yelling at me
I didn't do anything
Mercato oh can I put the upper trap for
the syusai table coconut pop was looking
at the husband completely wrong well he
had companies for meeting and sorry I'm
an urban Ursula
it is misunderstanding the husband you
are the luckiest Allah Muhammad to hunt
up Swami then at the same moment that
but a sudden sama is a misunderstanding
everything in the kitchen Ursula Panther
had a gala you need a Purdue cat the
refrigerator Lucas who paid for this job
my mumbly Colchis how did I get the
money for the refrigerator behind my
husband rain buggy - American public
will cost are the d-block and Swami's is
Cara
up wisdom shut up complexion ah it
understands the NRP oh I helped another
person buy something further home
therefore I have also I am a mentor
enlightenment bleed SWAT on to roam
America or like a night to sleep when
your focus but misunderstand the P
xalapa hum looks at the family had
Colchis
that's my it to go casaya why kenapa I
work for money I bought there if you
sire but kilometer but can once a mobile
ecosystem it obras already taco now if
you don't understand that your husband
yelling is coming from you chica under
the monarchy Bower Swami and Egbert
rocky to Brussels Dariana and if you
don't understand that you got the
refrigerator in your kitchen because you
help someone else to get something then
you can't even dirty bomb under my milk
you could cast it up or come on dammit
comes to swathi you get angry about
husband then under marauding on Swami
toe and if someone tries to take your
refugee
the cursor on it one company in the
wheel of life in the Wheel of Life is
always the name of the wheel of life is
suffering Wheel of Life
makanda I got that abroad idiotic a dupe
under a decade once lalu
but RT road happen the rattan throw
depend upon okay so now we can go to the
text Mariquita Masuka tax merrick pay
misunderstanding things like this merit
pay Casa la palma notice on a super day
me that husband also me too
comes from his diab result there is
hideous until he decided to get mama to
schematic mera kaam means or comic for
means or looks at this chill doesn't
mean diamond come brother a pouch Allah
making a chilled in the kitchen
chewy needed a Bharata Dharma tepee
object did a poor like the refugees
particle cos that that came from the
store only to Brussels there is token I
bought it with my mind's eye a mumbly I
didn't want so dear a misunderstanding
doesn't understand that I have a
refrigerator because I got money because
I helped other people to give money to
xalapa mantilla monarchy bába sáí bába
cool
casaya Ponyo Wonka now say ah mama
Thorin Leonard Achmed up a cannula then
I'll get Seneca two birds in it holds
that the husband exists out there from
his own son
Cambodian do Cobra panda padmaja Swamy
brother de lure son and heir is sicinius
on the air holes that the refrigerates
out there from its own side then do come
a bacon pecan Randhawa cookus on the
divorce Onodera sicinius endearing and
the pen pen adapt under a banner then
Rick by year she done gentle moon girl
those two states of mind are in direct
contradiction to I couldn't because I
need to add Allah contradicts a table
one and Sarah a long song wisdom says
Oksana magnet at all my husband's
yelling at me cuz I yell at my kids
nursery also my cyber tree at Panasonic
and Isaiah Burt Riyadh panic ninguna
wisdom says young son and manga talkin I
have a refrigerator in my kitchen
because I have someone else to get some
money
same ammonia cool custody up or
connoisseur moment or online no domina
but can do one
ignorance things Kabuto Harbor Pekin
sorry
misunderstanding masala burger can burp
it for no reason
dear brothers I attend palace and that
we figure then Cole Cassie to sabotage
American public assistance today a
delicate antique Iran and one of them is
completely mistake than selasa tuna
burner burner clear ooh
therefore only carmine till we call it
miss understanding katomina but now
sunup 'him and it's kind of like they
mean mumble or double sugar and that's a
similar gun in America none to a person
who doesn't know what's going on at all
they are completely blind like my dog
Theo SACEUR on yanti dr. painter jadi
recombinant minar butas portaging
science eel
and if you are blind in this in this way
if you are blind about what's real dan
juga nobuta Tessera any and abuta panda
Appa Appa my blind stepmom she falls off
steps and she recently she cut open her
chin a booty sang Moo dah dah dah dah
dah rectangle Barberini maluca da cunha
and my blind dog he walks around the
house he hits his head on the wall and
Angie buta saya
the average Alaska Talmud and capelin
German toward ending those people who
don't have wisdom or I wanted a mammal
be Jackson on misunderstand the
husband and Salah pumpkin dance for me
that cook us in that sense they are
blind
given our t to break abuta
then pebble company says you know what
there's two kinds of this kind of
misunderstood lupa baccarat bunch of
ricotta and that time I didn't discuss
Alabama's pendulum Oh madam
some people don't understand come on I
did who are all wrong auntie that
McCarty karma they don't understand the
husband came from what they did before
but I got to the monarchy by was Swamy
Nebraska hurry up America lakukan
sebelum Nia they don't even know about
America back on deduct out on the Karma
maybe I heard the word or karma really
became a company car cut out and on
karma a yearly they have no idea McCarty
ducked out and Tunku come Karma
so that's one kind of blindness here
it's called darkness kadhi to Lassa
Lassa to jhinezka boot an invisible cat
clapping and there's the second color
miss and mr. moody another Jenny skidoo
ie to Casa la palma about emptiness that
danke course on the real nature of
things
sefa yep Teresa galas how to put it very
clearly simply and correctly took mum
what their sanity luster honored and
Bernard
the husband I thought was in the kitchen
shaumyan saya picker brother dedapper
the husband who yelled at me for no
reason
Swamy metropolis ayat and policin that
husband was never in the kitchen he's
not in the kitchen
he will never be in the kitchen because
he cannot exist Swami to teleport
Nandita porta de la braderie depress
Karan dat da camp Ranade adapt or karna
deity Renata
so two kinds of not knowing today I did
one is Theta Tau number one number Tama
do you know about karma the laws of
karma the rules of criminal a packet out
on the Karma home karma and karma no I
never study table porn I'm obliged arena
okay and then the second kind that
completely discard what do you realize
that the husband is sad in the kitchen
was never in the kitchen apakah Dada
Reba was Swami another picture that did
operate to tada Bernadette it up or so
obviously the second one is more
dangerous the ditch Alaskan can do Anila
people behind you can hit your head on
the wall more strong couple our visitor
Penelope quad did ending
okay we have a few minutes left okay get
up on your butt butt up on my knees
lucky second link at the wheel but I get
a lot just kinda cut out Annika do ro
dah which is called fresh karma you nice
Abud karma cigar and the picture is a
Potter making plans that Gambardella
Sauron come but cramming
there's a very simple example of fresh
caramel undertone joining us Brandon
karma Segura
fresh karma is the seed you planted in
your mind just now karma cigar Adela
baby tomorrow under panel appearance
Cara
in the kitchen your husband call you
stupid did a push for me and Emma
monkeyland a Buddha and you say I'm not
stupid you stupid under capacity Roberto
and I am bored oh you're
misunderstanding about the husband just
caused you to do the link number 1 cause
link number 2 under saw a bumpkin done
Swamy Hyneman you're buckin and down the
block who can doubt on a more subtle
mini-map control Nakamura can undermine
what karma berry yes Danny $400 Einstein
Leon took photos dollar yep we think
there was some pickle can do low I
forgot the salut Perpignan yeah yeah so
she doesn't understand husband
misunderstood
did he appear among artists for Mina
this tiny mind says I be killin a pom
economy lakukan a pop again but the size
of the misunderstanding minding number
one dwayne tancana castle apartment p
current outta number sad to oran muta
then she makes fresh cup lalu da bomb
but karma Segura she says I'm not stupid
than the other capacité de Bordeaux and
a Moodle she just put a new seed in
Jerusalem when I but can be been
borrowed Olympic Iranian what will
happen from that see a pelican tragedy
didn't BB D $200 quest tonyandsara to
Stoller
yeah when it opens Kappa Kappa Bukka
$50 this is swaminathan applaud allah dr
salam in a box Tonga Lima Pluto Lara
yeah yeah of course the husband mooyah
her but but a little vague idea is the
kids will be bad next to suggest for
American Bertrand padania to be in am
sorry Adela Annapurna I can break a lock
on New Rock mingled upon this community
I can but preparation is yakaar monogamy
big bar at zero open the Contra book
indeed a porter that's the wheel of
Gotama milky by Nexon cirrhosis rocket
chiller by necrotic achill so but right
now in the kitchen poppies are indeed a
poor that seed is still fresh come
bibbity to my see karma cigar and you
know I like to garden then I decide to
come back up wound
I enjoyed slanting watermelons I mean
absurd some ornaments this week inside
says so coming and I'm semana card and
minghui nice a common animal bra possum
on coming we need the seed under the
dirt critic and atomically monitor can
be D by 1 mm Oh Mordor
that's making new parts if - mom what
pot borrow so let's go to the text but I
get a muskrat backs me but do chain near
the second link of of the wheel which is
called making fresh coma talkin kuduro
die and this about mum what karma cigar
legged share pitar it's just like
working like new things
it is super typical just but him
embankments are too
marek bacon a long day you are motivated
by your misunderstanding of your husband
under motif Osceola Castle a pomander
Haddad Swami
then you do things then undocumented
Madhu chill 8 opinion B and you do Carmo
which is gonna produce a new body in
mind for you in the next table Coogan
car Maya Akkad maja silicon too pedantic
Aaron burundi recently read agreed-upon
drakonia
you are like a Potter who's making pots
for the next night and there's a per
diem what pot Damon but pot and okay -
pants London
and there are three traditional kinds of
karma you can make eidetic adidas karma
traditionally under be somewhat and this
is a little different from the usual
presentation in its ticket Burberry they
represent a sepia Sonia
usually we just say you're good karma is
what produces happy things in your life
Bassanio tiny'mon talkin karma bike
Aguila appium hassel can howl howl
mahidol Amitabh under their cameras
where it makes their things in then
karma brew Candela penguin what Hal
Holbrook Darin Peter Panda and neutral
karma made these little lines and this
coffee cup that nobody cares about karma
net remember Gary Scott chilled its
anchor company and didn t / doulica nor
ahora
but here we have a slightly different
traditional presentation a parasitic
otama maliki present us a traditionalist
wicked bro beta Lendl on monday model
bacon a long day if you have this kind
of misunderstanding where you never
learned about karma and the result of
karma chicken Dominica jealous Casa la
palma de banana tournament on karma the
russell berrie karma if you if you never
know if you never had the good seats to
meet a teacher who taught you about
Karma
you can't attend a purnama maliki babied
by Cotto Burton Buddhist or angry I'm
gonna gherkin and um I'll make the
psyllium member it's called cinema
member brie and under come on what so
now mind peyote bad day and I can lock
on Hal Holbrook kill people my boy
but boho still mystery but if you kind
of missing you can double Maliki to
discus Allah Mohammed Lumumba America
which doesn't understand the real nature
of your husband until upon Muhammad and
Salmonella there is Swami anda the
dependent origination of your husband
that he came from some but a key but for
me and embrace all the rotten cannibal
panda Panda that's a different kind of
misunderstanding it was such a nice bump
Salah permanent life possible those
people can do good deeds done it to look
into kaorun but button bag you got
there's such a thing as it's good this
which your mom taught you to do the
whole bike young support ideas are
cannoli boo on that a panda to the
monarchy karma so you do good things
addendum lakukan Howell my record is
broken is about karma by quarter you
don't understand and did a monarchy up a
gondola cook and an atom la cocaina
those will take you to a good place
which will finish because you don't know
maricon Mambo under curtain but I can I
can hobbies Khan and Attila coming up
under brother dishonor
so many of the good actions that people
do are not good the deben acted i can
buy kia ora ora laka conn-young
Buchan karma by Jacob rocketed up
another Bernardo Guardi so these three
words in in Tibetan cinema theoretical
kata de la maza Tibet Salaam nonce
Buchan Sunnah and then we call on
shifting commerce a drama which will not
deter to another place communicators
about karma that burger sir Cameron
tipped carmine did I can't be negative
but line
first one is 30 good yeah palma de la
karma by quarter yeah you're gonna go
someplace pretty good
yeah under masuka's wanted competent to
compare their study and a conman dorita
Nissan and Yuka then or you do back home
Anton damn luck when karma guru it
doesn't matter where you go first you go
to what we call the desire that get up a
duly commanded a perky and I can /
kicker potato somebody occurring in done
then a condom underneath it's kind of a
pretty strong copier there's so much um
comma bike and took up quad here is
called me only know this about me Ola it
will take you to the formula or the
formulas room which we talked about in
your car mobile under Allen bourbon took
her to a lamp and pump in Tokyo so lucky
to meet Sarah can today
and that karma is so good that it is so
strong that it won't did for and carmine
to begin to bike but get to court
deduction pinda but still is he
suffering capital top such a toward
Allah Karmapa Narita ok so there we have
the first two things this syndicate are
they do a Totten pertama and I did among
artists from yonder so you you're back
did he end up were three akan Valley
padania yeah what's that gonna cost and
ENIAC adamant about kenapa find out in
session
sorry this SE tu hablas see you later
and thank you standing sub a jumper and
Rima consistently
this